var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "forever",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "forever",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(by) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your fathers",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ābāakum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your fathers",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ābāukum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَبِيهِ",
        "answer": "for his father",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "li-abīhi",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَأْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "but refuse",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "watabā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَأْبَى",
        "answer": "but Allah refuses",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayabā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "Allah brings",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "they come",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "yatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "come to them",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "yatihim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "Came to them",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "atathum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَوْكَ",
        "answer": "they came to you",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "atawka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَوُا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "waātawū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَوُا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "waātawū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَى",
        "answer": "and gives",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "waātā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah gave them",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "ātāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُؤْتِينَا",
        "answer": "Allah will give us",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "sayu'tīnā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "wayu'tūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَانَا",
        "answer": "He gives us",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "ātānā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "He gave them",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "ātāhum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَ",
        "answer": "the reward",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ajra",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "any",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَى",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخُذُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "and seize them",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wakhudhūhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "we took",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذْ",
        "answer": "Take",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "khudh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَأْخُذُ",
        "answer": "and takes",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wayakhudhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "They have taken",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "takes",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "and takes",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "wayattakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the hereafter",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and (in) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and (in) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "And others",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "waākharūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخَرَ",
        "answer": "(with) other",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "waākhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "And others",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "waākharūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِخْوَانُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then (they are) your brothers",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fa-ikh'wānukum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِخْوَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your brothers",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'wānakum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِخْوَانُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your brothers",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'wānukum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "[when]",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "if",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And whenever",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And whenever",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذِنْتَ",
        "answer": "you grant leave",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "adhinta",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "ائْذَنْ",
        "answer": "Grant me leave",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "i'dhan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُؤْذَنَ",
        "answer": "that permission be granted",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "liyu'dhana",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَأْذِنُكَ",
        "answer": "(Would) not ask your permission",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yastadhinuka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَأْذِنُكَ",
        "answer": "ask your leave",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yastadhinuka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَأْذَنُوكَ",
        "answer": "and they ask you permission",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tadhanūka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَأْذَنَكَ",
        "answer": "ask your permission",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "is'tadhanaka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَأْذِنُونَكَ",
        "answer": "ask your permission",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yastadhinūnaka",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَذَانٌ",
        "answer": "And an announcement",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wa-adhānun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُذُنٌ",
        "answer": "(all) ear",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "udhunun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُذُنُ",
        "answer": "An ear",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "udhunu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْذُونَ",
        "answer": "hurt",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yu'dhūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْذُونَ",
        "answer": "hurt",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yu'dhūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُسِّسَ",
        "answer": "founded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ussisa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَّسَ",
        "answer": "founded",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "assasa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَّسَ",
        "answer": "founded",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "assasa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْفَكُونَ",
        "answer": "deluded are they",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yu'fakūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the towns overturned",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'tafikāti",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "surely eat",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "layakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤَلَّفَةِ",
        "answer": "and the ones inclined",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wal-mu-alafati",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلًّا",
        "answer": "(of) kinship",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "illan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلًّا",
        "answer": "(of) kinship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "illan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "If not",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "If not",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those (with) whom",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) those who",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those (with) whom",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those (with) whom",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "500",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Like those",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "513",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "like the one who",
        "pcklId": "514",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "516",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "517",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "522",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "526",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "527",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "528",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "[those] who",
        "pcklId": "529",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "530",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "531",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "532",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "533",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1454",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "1455",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "(with) a painful punishment",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "One God",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1252",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1253",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1254",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "from Allah",
        "pcklId": "1255",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1256",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1257",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1258",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1259",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the) Words of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1260",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1261",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1262",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "[with] the Verses of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1263",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "But Allah",
        "pcklId": "1264",
        "tlit": "fal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will punish them",
        "pcklId": "1265",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah accepts repentance",
        "pcklId": "1266",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1267",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah made evident",
        "pcklId": "1268",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "1269",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1270",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the) masajid of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1271",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the) masajid of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1272",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1273",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1274",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1275",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1276",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1277",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1278",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1279",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1280",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1281",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1282",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah brings",
        "pcklId": "1283",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1284",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah helped you",
        "pcklId": "1285",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "1286",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah accepts repentance",
        "pcklId": "1287",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1288",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will enrich you",
        "pcklId": "1289",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1290",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1291",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "1292",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1293",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1294",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(May) Allah destroy them",
        "pcklId": "1295",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1296",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah s light",
        "pcklId": "1297",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "but Allah refuses",
        "pcklId": "1298",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1299",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1300",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1301",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1302",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1303",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "1304",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "1305",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1306",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1307",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1308",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah helped him",
        "pcklId": "1309",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1310",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Then Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "1311",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1312",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1313",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1314",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1315",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1316",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(May) Allah forgive",
        "pcklId": "1317",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1318",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1319",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1320",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah disliked",
        "pcklId": "1321",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1322",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the) Order of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1323",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has decreed",
        "pcklId": "1324",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1325",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will afflict you",
        "pcklId": "1326",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1327",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah intends",
        "pcklId": "1328",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1329",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah gave them",
        "pcklId": "1330",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1331",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will give us",
        "pcklId": "1332",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1333",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1334",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1335",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1336",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1337",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1338",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1339",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1340",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1341",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1342",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Is it Allah",
        "pcklId": "1343",
        "tlit": "abil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1344",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "1345",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah has cursed them",
        "pcklId": "1346",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1347",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1348",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will have mercy on them",
        "pcklId": "1349",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1350",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1351",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1352",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1353",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah had enriched them",
        "pcklId": "1354",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will punish them",
        "pcklId": "1355",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(with) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1356",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(the covenant with) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1357",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1358",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1359",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will ridicule",
        "pcklId": "1360",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "will Allah forgive",
        "pcklId": "1361",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1362",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1363",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1364",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1365",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah returns you",
        "pcklId": "1366",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1367",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah intends",
        "pcklId": "1368",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1369",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has prepared",
        "pcklId": "1370",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1371",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1372",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1373",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah sealed",
        "pcklId": "1374",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah (has) informed us",
        "pcklId": "1375",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah will see",
        "pcklId": "1376",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1377",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1378",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah (has) revealed",
        "pcklId": "1379",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1380",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1381",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1382",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1383",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will admit them",
        "pcklId": "1384",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1385",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah is pleased",
        "pcklId": "1386",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1387",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1388",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1389",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1390",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1391",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "then Allah will see",
        "pcklId": "1392",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "for the Command of Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1393",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1394",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(against) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1395",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "But Allah",
        "pcklId": "1396",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1397",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1398",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1399",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1400",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1401",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1402",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1403",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1404",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1405",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(for) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1406",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1407",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1408",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "1409",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah turned (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "1410",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1411",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1412",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1413",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1414",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1415",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1416",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "that Allah may reward them",
        "pcklId": "1417",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1418",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has turned away",
        "pcklId": "1419",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1420",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "until",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِرُوا",
        "answer": "they were commanded",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "umirū",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُونَ",
        "answer": "They enjoin",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yamurūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُونَ",
        "answer": "They enjoin",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yamurūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "His Command",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "bi-amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمُورَ",
        "answer": "the matters",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-umūra",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرُ",
        "answer": "(the) Order of Allah",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرَنَا",
        "answer": "our matter",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "amranā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَمْرِ",
        "answer": "for the Command of Allah ",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "li-amri",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآمِرُونَ",
        "answer": "those who enjoin",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "l-āmirūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِمَّةَ",
        "answer": "the leaders",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "a-immata",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "As for",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَّا",
        "answer": "whether",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "he believes",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "and believes",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "wayu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنَ",
        "answer": "we will believe",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "nu'mina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَأْمَنَهُ",
        "answer": "(to) his place of safety",
        "pcklId": "585",
        "tlit": "mamanahu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِيمَانِ",
        "answer": "[the] belief",
        "pcklId": "622",
        "tlit": "l-īmāni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your belief",
        "pcklId": "623",
        "tlit": "īmānikum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) faith",
        "pcklId": "624",
        "tlit": "īmānan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) faith",
        "pcklId": "625",
        "tlit": "īmānan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنٍ",
        "answer": "a believer",
        "pcklId": "717",
        "tlit": "mu'minin",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "718",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "719",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "720",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "[so] let the believers put (their) trust",
        "pcklId": "721",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "722",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "723",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "And the believing men",
        "pcklId": "724",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the believing men",
        "pcklId": "725",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "726",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "and the believers",
        "pcklId": "727",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "728",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "729",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the believers",
        "pcklId": "730",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(for) the believers",
        "pcklId": "731",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "to the believers",
        "pcklId": "732",
        "tlit": "bil-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) believers",
        "pcklId": "845",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the believing women",
        "pcklId": "852",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'minātu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the believing women",
        "pcklId": "853",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'mināti",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "people",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(for) the people",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "li-ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "first",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلِ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "awwali",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "the first",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-awalūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولُو",
        "answer": "(the) men",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولِي",
        "answer": "near of kin",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَوَّاهٌ",
        "answer": "(was) compassionate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "la-awwāhun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَأْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And their abode",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wamawāhum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَأْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their abode",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wamawāhum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيَّدَهُ",
        "answer": "and supported him",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-ayyadahu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "[with] the Verses of Allah",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Verses",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Verses",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "waāyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "and wretched",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَخِلُوا",
        "answer": "they became stingy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bakhilū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَءُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "began (to attack) you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "badaūkum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَبْدِلْ",
        "answer": "and will replace you",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wayastabdil",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَرَّأَ",
        "answer": "he disassociated",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tabarra-a",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرَاءَةٌ",
        "answer": "Freedom from obligations",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "barāatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرِيءٌ",
        "answer": "(is) free from obligations",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "barīon",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "And give glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَشِّرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their Lord gives them glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yubashiruhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشِّرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "[so] give them tidings",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fabashir'hum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "And give glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَبْشِرُوا",
        "answer": "So rejoice",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tabshirū",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَبْشِرُونَ",
        "answer": "rejoice",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yastabshirūna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "in falsehood",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bil-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْبِعَاثَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their being sent",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "inbiʿāthahum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعُدَتْ",
        "answer": "was long",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baʿudat",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "(of) others",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْغُونَكُمُ",
        "answer": "seeking (for) you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yabghūnakumu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتَغَوُا",
        "answer": "they had sought",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ib'taghawū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَبْكُوا",
        "answer": "and let them weep",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walyabkū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْلِغْهُ",
        "answer": "escort him",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "abligh'hu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنَوْا",
        "answer": "they built",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "banaw",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْنَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your sons",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wa-abnāukum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "(is) son",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "(is) son",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنِ",
        "answer": "and the wayfarer ",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُنْيَانَهُ",
        "answer": "his building",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "bun'yānahu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُنْيَانَهُ",
        "answer": "his building",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "bun'yānahu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُنْيَانُهُمُ",
        "answer": "their building",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "bun'yānuhumu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَايَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have contracted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bāyaʿtum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَيْعِكُمُ",
        "answer": "in your transaction",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bibayʿikumu",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنَ",
        "answer": "He makes clear",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yubayyina",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "(became) evident",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yatabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "has become clear",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "it became clear",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "tabayyana",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "among",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاتَّبَعُوكَ",
        "answer": "surely they (would) have followed you",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "la-ittabaʿūka",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "followed them",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿūhum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعُوهُ",
        "answer": "followed him",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿūhu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتِجَارَةٌ",
        "answer": "and the commerce",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "watijāratun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتَهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taḥtahā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُتْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "you would be left",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tut'rakū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتِمُّوا",
        "answer": "so fulfil",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fa-atimmū",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتِمَّ",
        "answer": "perfect",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yutimma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you repent",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tub'tum",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابُوا",
        "answer": "they repent",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "tābū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابُوا",
        "answer": "they repent",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "tābū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "And Allah accepts repentance",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wayatūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "Allah accepts repentance",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yatūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُوا",
        "answer": "they repent",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yatūbū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبَ",
        "answer": "will turn (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yatūba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "He will turn (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yatūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "Allah turned (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "He turned (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "He turned (in mercy)",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَتُوبُوا",
        "answer": "that they may repent",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "liyatūbū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُونَ",
        "answer": "they turn (in repentance)",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yatūbūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوْبَةَ",
        "answer": "the repentance",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-tawbata",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّائِبُونَ",
        "answer": "Those who turn in repentance",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "al-tāibūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Acceptor of repentance",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّوَّابُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Acceptor of repentance",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-tawābu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَثَبَّطَهُمْ",
        "answer": "so He made them lag behind",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fathabbaṭahum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثَّاقَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you cling heavily",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ithāqaltum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثِقَالًا",
        "answer": "or heavy",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wathiqālan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّلَاثَةِ",
        "answer": "the three",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-thalāthati",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "(for) a little price",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَا",
        "answer": "(is) twelve",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ith'nā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَانِيَ",
        "answer": "the second",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "thāniya",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِبَاهُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their foreheads",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jibāhuhum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْدَرُ",
        "answer": "and more likely",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ajdaru",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُرُفٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a cliff",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jurufin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "criminals",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flows",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flows",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَجْزِيَهُمُ",
        "answer": "that Allah may reward them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "liyajziyahumu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is) the recompense",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "(as) a recompense",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "a recompense",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِزْيَةَ",
        "answer": "the jizyah",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "l-jiz'yata",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَعَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you make",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ajaʿaltum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْمَحُونَ",
        "answer": "run wild",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajmaḥūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their flanks",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wajunūbuhum",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنُودًا",
        "answer": "forces",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "junūdan",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجُنُودٍ",
        "answer": "with forces",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bijunūdin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "and Gardens",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wajannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "jannāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "(is) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "strive",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "jāhadū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهَدَ",
        "answer": "and strives",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wajāhada",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "and strove",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wajāhadū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهِدُوا",
        "answer": "and strive",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wajāhidū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَاهِدُوا",
        "answer": "they strive",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yujāhidū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهِدِ",
        "answer": "Strive (against)",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "jāhidi",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَاهِدُوا",
        "answer": "strive",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yujāhidū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهِدُوا",
        "answer": "and strive",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wajāhidū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاهَدُوا",
        "answer": "strove",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "jāhadū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجِهَادٍ",
        "answer": "and striving",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wajihādin",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُهْدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their effort",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "juh'dahum",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَجِرْهُ",
        "answer": "then grant him protection",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-ajir'hu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَجَارَكَ",
        "answer": "seek your protection",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "is'tajāraka",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And came",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(has) come to you",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّونَ",
        "answer": "who love",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbūna",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَحَبُّوا",
        "answer": "they prefer",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "is'taḥabbū",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَبَّ",
        "answer": "(are) more beloved",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "aḥabba",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْبَارَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their rabbis",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aḥbārahum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَحْبَارِ",
        "answer": "the rabbis",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-aḥbāri",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَتْ",
        "answer": "worthless",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَتْ",
        "answer": "worthless",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the greater Pilgrimage",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاجِّ",
        "answer": "(to) the pilgrims",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāji",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَادِدِ",
        "answer": "opposes",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yuḥādidi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُدُودَ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥudūda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِحُدُودِ",
        "answer": "(the) limits",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "liḥudūdi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْذَرُ",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaḥdharu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taḥdharūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "beware",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaḥdharūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَارَبَ",
        "answer": "warred",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥāraba",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٌ",
        "answer": "any blame",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥarajun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرِّ",
        "answer": "the heat",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ḥari",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرًّا",
        "answer": "(in) heat",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥarran",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرِيصٌ",
        "answer": "(he is) concerned",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥarīṣun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَرِّمُونَ",
        "answer": "they make unlawful",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yuḥarrimūna",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحَرِّمُونَهُ",
        "answer": "and make it unlawful",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wayuḥarrimūnahu",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "Allah has made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُرُمُ",
        "answer": "the sacred months",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-ḥurumu",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرُمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) sacred",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ḥurumun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنْ",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "taḥzan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَزَنًا",
        "answer": "(of) sorrow",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ḥazanan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "(do) you think",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥasib'tum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسْبُنَا",
        "answer": "Sufficient for us",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ḥasbunā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسْبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "sufficient for them",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ḥasbuhum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسْبِيَ",
        "answer": "Sufficient for me",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ḥasbiya",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "the best",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَيَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two best (things)",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nayayni",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةٌ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِحْسَانٍ",
        "answer": "in righteousness",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "bi-iḥ'sānin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحْصُرُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "and besiege them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-uḥ'ṣurūhum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحَافِظُونَ",
        "answer": "and those who observe",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥāfiẓūna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(has) more right",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(have) more right",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more worthy",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the truth",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] truth",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "true",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَيَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "And they will swear",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wasayaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "And they swear",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wayaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "They swear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "They swear",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "They will swear",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "sayaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "They swear",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaḥlifūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَحْلِفُنَّ",
        "answer": "And surely they will swear",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "walayaḥlifunna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِلُّونَهُ",
        "answer": "They make it lawful",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yuḥillūnahu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُحِلُّوا",
        "answer": "and making lawful",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fayuḥillū",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "forbearing",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَامِدُونَ",
        "answer": "those who praise",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāmidūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَحْمِلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "that you provide them with mounts",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "litaḥmilahum",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْمِلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "to mount you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aḥmilukum",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "it will be heated [on it]",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'mā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُحِيطَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will) surely surround",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "lamuḥīṭatun",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "around you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥawlakum",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "were around them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥawlahum",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "He gives life",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "with the life",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the life",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْبَارِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your news",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "akhbārikum",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبَالًا",
        "answer": "(in) confusion",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khabālan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَخَرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "certainly we (would) have come forth",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "lakharajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجُوا",
        "answer": "they (had) gone forth",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "kharajū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُجُوا",
        "answer": "will you come out",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "takhrujū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَهُ",
        "answer": "drove him out",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "akhrajahu",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُرُوجَ",
        "answer": "(to) go forth",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-khurūja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْخُرُوجِ",
        "answer": "to go out",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "lil'khurūji",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِخْرَاجِ",
        "answer": "to drive out",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "bi-ikh'rāji",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْرِجٌ",
        "answer": "(will) bring forth",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "mukh'rijun",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُخْزِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and disgrace them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wayukh'zihim",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِزْيُ",
        "answer": "(is) the disgrace",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-khiz'yu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْزِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who (will) disgrace",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mukh'zī",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَخْشَوْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you fear them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "atakhshawnahum",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَوْهُ",
        "answer": "you should fear Him",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "takhshawhu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yakhsha",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "takhshawna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِفَافًا",
        "answer": "light",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khifāfan",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(They will) abide",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدًا",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "khālidan",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "they (will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "will abide",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَطُوا",
        "answer": "They had mixed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khalaṭū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِّفُوا",
        "answer": "were left behind",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khullifū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْلَفُوا",
        "answer": "they broke",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "akhlafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَخَلَّفُوا",
        "answer": "they remain behind",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yatakhallafū",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَافَ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "khilāfa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَوَالِفِ",
        "answer": "those who stay behind",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-khawālifi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَوَالِفِ",
        "answer": "those who stay behind",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-khawālifi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِفِينَ",
        "answer": "those who stay behind",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-khālifīna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخَلَّفُونَ",
        "answer": "those who remained behind",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-mukhalafūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "He created",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَلَاقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their portion",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "bikhalāqihim",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَلَاقِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your portion",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "bikhalāqikum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَلَاقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their portion",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "bikhalāqihim",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَالَكُمْ",
        "answer": "in your midst",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khilālakum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَلُّوا",
        "answer": "then leave",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fakhallū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَخْمَصَةٌ",
        "answer": "hunger",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "makhmaṣatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخُوضُ",
        "answer": "conversing",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nakhūḍu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخُضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you indulge",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wakhuḍ'tum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاضُوا",
        "answer": "indulges (in idle talk)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khāḍū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "khif'tum",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "best",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) goodness",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرَاتُ",
        "answer": "(are) the good things",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "l-khayrātu",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْبِرِينَ",
        "answer": "fleeing",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "mud'birīna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُدْخِلُهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will admit them",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "sayud'khiluhumu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدَّخَلًا",
        "answer": "a place to enter",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "muddakhalan",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَةً",
        "answer": "(in) rank",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "darajatan",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّمْعِ",
        "answer": "(with) the tears",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-damʿi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَائِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(will be) the turn",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "dāiratu",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّوَائِرَ",
        "answer": "the turns (of misfortune)",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-dawāira",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدِينُونَ",
        "answer": "they acknowledge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yadīnūna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "[the] religion",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "dīnikum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) religion",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدِينِ",
        "answer": "and the religion",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wadīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "all religions",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينُ",
        "answer": "(is) the religion",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-dīnu",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "pay heed",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "yadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِمَّةً",
        "answer": "covenant of protection",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dhimmatan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِمَّةً",
        "answer": "covenant of protection",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dhimmatan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their sins",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُذْهِبْ",
        "answer": "And remove",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wayudh'hib",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذَّهَبَ",
        "answer": "the gold",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-dhahaba",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذُوقُوا",
        "answer": "so taste",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fadhūqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Most Kind",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "raūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(he is) kind",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "raūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَوْهَا",
        "answer": "which you did not see",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "tarawhā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَوْهَا",
        "answer": "which you did not see",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "tarawhā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَيَرَى",
        "answer": "and Allah will see",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wasayarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيَرَى",
        "answer": "then Allah will see",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "fasayarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "see you",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yarākum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their Lord gives them glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "rabbuhum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَابًا",
        "answer": "(as) Lords",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "arbāban",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(is the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَبَّصُوا",
        "answer": "then wait",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fatarabbaṣū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَبَّصُونَ",
        "answer": "you await",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tarabbaṣūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَرَبَّصُ",
        "answer": "[we] await",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "natarabbaṣu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَبَّصُوا",
        "answer": "So wait",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fatarabbaṣū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَتَرَبَّصُ",
        "answer": "and he awaits",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayatarabbaṣu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَرَبِّصُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) waiting",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "mutarabbiṣūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةَ",
        "answer": "(during) four",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "arbaʿata",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعَةٌ",
        "answer": "four",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "arbaʿatun",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسٌ",
        "answer": "(are) impure",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "rij'sun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسًا",
        "answer": "(in) evil",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "rij'san",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their evil",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "rij'sihim",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجَعَكَ",
        "answer": "Allah returns you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "rajaʿaka",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you (have) returned",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "rajaʿtum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجَعُوا",
        "answer": "they return",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "rajaʿū",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالٌ",
        "answer": "(are) men",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "rijālun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْجَوْنَ",
        "answer": "deferred",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "mur'jawna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحُبَتْ",
        "answer": "(in spite) of its vastness",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "raḥubat",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحُبَتْ",
        "answer": "it was vast",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "raḥubat",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَرْحَمُهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will have mercy on them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sayarḥamuhumu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "of Mercy",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "biraḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and (is) a mercy",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(and) merciful",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَدُّونَ",
        "answer": "you will be brought back",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "turaddūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرَدُّونَ",
        "answer": "they will be returned",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yuraddūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَتُرَدُّونَ",
        "answer": "And you will be brought back",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wasaturaddūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَدَّدُونَ",
        "answer": "they waver",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yataraddadūna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلَ",
        "answer": "has sent",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "arsala",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and (so is) His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "rasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and in His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "wabirasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Messengers",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "rusuluhum",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْصَدٍ",
        "answer": "place of ambush",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "marṣadin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِرْصَادًا",
        "answer": "and (as) a station",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'ṣādan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَوْنَهَا",
        "answer": "you delight (in) it",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tarḍawnahā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَضِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "Are you pleased",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "araḍītum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضُوا",
        "answer": "they are pleased",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "raḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضُوا",
        "answer": "(were) satisfied",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "raḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "were satisfied",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "raḍītum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضُوا",
        "answer": "They (were) satisfied",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "raḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضُوا",
        "answer": "They (are) satisfied",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "raḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَرْضَوْا",
        "answer": "that you may be pleased",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "litarḍaw",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْضَوْا",
        "answer": "you are pleased",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tarḍaw",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) not pleased",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yarḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضِيَ",
        "answer": "Allah is pleased",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "raḍiya",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَضُوا",
        "answer": "and they are pleased",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "waraḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْضُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "They satisfy you",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yur'ḍūnakum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُرْضُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "to please you",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "liyur'ḍūkum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْضُوهُ",
        "answer": "they should please Him",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yur'ḍūhu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانٍ",
        "answer": "and Pleasure",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانٌ",
        "answer": "But the pleasure",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانٍ",
        "answer": "and (His) pleasure",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْغَبُوا",
        "answer": "they prefer",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yarghabū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاغِبُونَ",
        "answer": "turn our hopes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "rāghibūna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْقُبُوا",
        "answer": "they do not regard (the ties)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarqubū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْقُبُونَ",
        "answer": "they respect (the ties)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yarqubūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّقَابِ",
        "answer": "the (freeing of) the necks",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-riqābi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّاكِعُونَ",
        "answer": "those who bow down",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-rākiʿūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُهْبَانَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their monks",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waruh'bānahum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرُّهْبَانِ",
        "answer": "and the monks",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-ruh'bāni",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "They want",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادُوا",
        "answer": "they had wished",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "arādū",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "Allah intends",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "Allah intends",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَدْنَا",
        "answer": "we wish",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "aradnā",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْتَابَتْ",
        "answer": "and (are in) doubts",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'tābat",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their doubts",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "raybihim",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِيبَةً",
        "answer": "a (cause of) doubt",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "rībatan",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُزَكِّيهِمْ",
        "answer": "and cause them increase",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "watuzakkīhim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَزْهَقَ",
        "answer": "and should depart",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watazhaqa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَزْهَقَ",
        "answer": "and will depart",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "watazhaqa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَزْوَاجُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your spouses",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-azwājukum",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَادُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they (would) have increased you",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "zādūkum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَادَتْهُ",
        "answer": "(has) increased [it]",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "zādathu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَزَادَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "then it has increased them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fazādathum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَزَادَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "(it) increases them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fazādathum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِيَادَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) an increase",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ziyādatun",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِيغُ",
        "answer": "deviated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yazīghu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزَالُ",
        "answer": "(will) cease",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yazālu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُيِّنَ",
        "answer": "Is made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "zuyyina",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you ask them",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "sa-altahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glory be to Him",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعِينَ",
        "answer": "seventy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sabʿīna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّابِقُونَ",
        "answer": "And the forerunners",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wal-sābiqūna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their way",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "sabīlahum",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His way",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His way",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "and the wayfarer ",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلٍ",
        "answer": "way (for blame)",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "sabīlin",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلُ",
        "answer": "the way (blame)",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-sabīlu",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاجِدَ",
        "answer": "(the) masajid of Allah",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "masājida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاجِدَ",
        "answer": "(the) masajid of Allah",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "masājida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "(of) Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدَ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-masjida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْجِدًا",
        "answer": "a masjid",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "masjidan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَسْجِدٌ",
        "answer": "A masjid",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "lamasjidun",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "those who prostrate",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-sājidūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَسْخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "so they ridicule",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fayaskharūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخِرَ",
        "answer": "Allah will ridicule",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sakhira",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْخَطُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) enraged",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaskhaṭūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِرَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their secret",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "sirrahum",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَفَرًا",
        "answer": "and a journey",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wasafaran",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّفْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "the lowest",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-suf'lā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَقَطُوا",
        "answer": "they have fallen",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "saqaṭū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِقَايَةَ",
        "answer": "the providing of water",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "siqāyata",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكَنٌ",
        "answer": "(are a) reassurance",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "sakanun",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكِينَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His tranquility",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "sakīnatahu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكِينَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His tranquility",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "sakīnatahu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَسَاكِنُ",
        "answer": "and the dwellings",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wamasākinu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَسَاكِنَ",
        "answer": "and dwellings",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wamasākina",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَسَاكِينِ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wal-masākīni",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْسَلَخَ",
        "answer": "have passed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "insalakha",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْلَامِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their (pretense of) Islam",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "is'lāmihim",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعَ",
        "answer": "he hears",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿa",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَّاعُونَ",
        "answer": "who would have listened",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "sammāʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسُؤْهُمْ",
        "answer": "it distresses them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tasu'hum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءُ",
        "answer": "(the) evil",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "sūu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوْءِ",
        "answer": "(of) the evil",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-sawi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئًا",
        "answer": "(that was) evil",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "sayyi-an",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُورَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Surah",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sūratun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُورَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Surah",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sūratun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُورَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Surah",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "sūratun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُورَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Surah",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "sūratun",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاعَةِ",
        "answer": "(the) hour",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوُونَ",
        "answer": "They are not equal",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yastawūna",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسِيحُوا",
        "answer": "So move about",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fasīḥū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّائِحُونَ",
        "answer": "those who go out",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-sāiḥūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدَّ",
        "answer": "mightier",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ashadda",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more intense",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(are) stronger",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "for the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "lil'mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "for the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "lil'mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "for the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "lil'mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَوْا",
        "answer": "They exchange",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ish'taraw",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(has) purchased",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ish'tarā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفَا",
        "answer": "edge",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shafā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَشْفِ",
        "answer": "and will heal",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayashfi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشُّقَّةُ",
        "answer": "the distance",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-shuqatu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُ",
        "answer": "bears witness",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yashhadu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "and the seen",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "wal-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "and the seen",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wal-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(while) witnessing",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْهُرٍ",
        "answer": "months",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ashhurin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَشْهُرُ",
        "answer": "the sacred months",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ashhuru",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشُّهُورِ",
        "answer": "(of) the months",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-shuhūri",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهْرًا",
        "answer": "months",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "shahran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in any) thing",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "and (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِصَاحِبِهِ",
        "answer": "to his companion",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "liṣāḥibihi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَدُّوا",
        "answer": "and they hinder (people)",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "faṣaddū",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَصُدُّونَ",
        "answer": "and hinder",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wayaṣuddūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورَ",
        "answer": "(the) breasts",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṣudūra",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقُوا",
        "answer": "were truthful",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqū",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَصَّدَّقَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely we will give charity",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "lanaṣṣaddaqanna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتِ",
        "answer": "the charities",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتُ",
        "answer": "the charities",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqātu",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتِ",
        "answer": "the charities",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدَقَاتِ",
        "answer": "the charities",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadaqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَةً",
        "answer": "a charity",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqatan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "those who are truthful",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرَفَ",
        "answer": "Allah has turned away",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣarafa",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْصَرَفُوا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "inṣarafū",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَغِيرَةً",
        "answer": "small",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṣaghīratan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاغِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) subdued",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣāghirūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحٌ",
        "answer": "righteous",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥun",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصَلِّ",
        "answer": "you pray",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tuṣalli",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَلِّ",
        "answer": "and bless",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waṣalli",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "(to) the prayer",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَلَوَاتِ",
        "answer": "and blessings",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "waṣalawāti",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَاتَكَ",
        "answer": "your blessings",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ṣalataka",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِبْكَ",
        "answer": "befalls you",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "tuṣib'ka",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِبْكَ",
        "answer": "befalls you",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "tuṣib'ka",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِيبَنَا",
        "answer": "will befall us",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yuṣībanā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِيبَكُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will afflict you",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yuṣībakumu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُصِيبُ",
        "answer": "Will strike",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "sayuṣību",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِيبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "afflict them",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yuṣībuhum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةٌ",
        "answer": "a calamity",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "muṣībatun",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the destination",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَضْحَكُوا",
        "answer": "So let them laugh",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "falyaḍḥakū",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضُرُّوهُ",
        "answer": "you can harm Him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taḍurrūhu",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِرَارًا",
        "answer": "(for causing) harm",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ḍirāran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضُّعَفَاءِ",
        "answer": "the weak",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ḍuʿafāi",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَلُّ",
        "answer": "are led astray",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yuḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُضِلَّ",
        "answer": "that He lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "liyuḍilla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَاهِئُونَ",
        "answer": "they imitate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuḍāhiūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضِيعُ",
        "answer": "allow to be lost",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yuḍīʿu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَاقَتْ",
        "answer": "and (was) straitened",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waḍāqat",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَاقَتْ",
        "answer": "(was) straitened",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḍāqat",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَاقَتْ",
        "answer": "And (was) straitened",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waḍāqat",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطُبِعَ",
        "answer": "and were sealed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waṭubiʿa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَبَعَ",
        "answer": "and Allah sealed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waṭabaʿa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَعَنُوا",
        "answer": "and defame",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waṭaʿanū",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطْفِئُوا",
        "answer": "extinguish",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuṭ'fiū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطَهِّرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "purifying them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tuṭahhiruhum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَطَهَّرُوا",
        "answer": "purify themselves",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yataṭahharū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُطَّهِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who purify themselves",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-muṭahirīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "and they obey",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wayuṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "we were able",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "is'taṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَوْعًا",
        "answer": "willingly",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ṭawʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُطَّوِّعِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who give willingly",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-muṭawiʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٍ",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatin",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةً",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٍ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatin",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "a party",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّوْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) wealth",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-ṭawli",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَةً",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibatan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظْلِمُوا",
        "answer": "wrong",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "taẓlimū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَظْلِمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "to wrong them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "liyaẓlimahum",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "doing wrong",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "of the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "bil-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoing people",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَمَأٌ",
        "answer": "thirst",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ẓama-on",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "and they were certain",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْهَرُوا",
        "answer": "they gain dominance",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaẓharū",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَهَرَ",
        "answer": "and became manifest",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waẓahara",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظَاهِرُوا",
        "answer": "they have supported",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yuẓāhirū",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُظْهِرَهُ",
        "answer": "to manifest it",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "liyuẓ'hirahu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظُهُورُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their backs",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "waẓuhūruhum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "that they worship",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "liyaʿbudū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَابِدُونَ",
        "answer": "those who worship",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "l-ʿābidūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَبَتْكُمْ",
        "answer": "pleased you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aʿjabatkum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْجِبْكَ",
        "answer": "impress you",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tuʿ'jib'ka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْجِبْكَ",
        "answer": "impress you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tuʿ'jib'ka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْجِزِي",
        "answer": "escape",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "muʿ'jizī",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْجِزِي",
        "answer": "escape",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "muʿ'jizī",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَعَدُّوا",
        "answer": "surely they (would) have prepared",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "la-aʿaddū",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعَدَّ",
        "answer": "Allah has prepared",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aʿadda",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعَدَّ",
        "answer": "And He has prepared",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿadda",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِدَّةَ",
        "answer": "(the) number",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿiddata",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِدَّةَ",
        "answer": "the number",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ʿiddata",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدَّةً",
        "answer": "(some) preparation",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ʿuddatan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "any enemy",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(was) an enemy",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٍّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwin",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-muʿ'tadūna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will punish them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'humu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "and He punished",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "waʿadhaba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will punish you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'kum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُعَذِّبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "to punish them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "liyuʿadhibahum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعَذِّبْ",
        "answer": "We will punish",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nuʿadhib",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will punish them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'humu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "punish them",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibahum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنُعَذِّبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "We will punish them",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "sanuʿadhibuhum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He will punish them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibuhum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "of a punishment",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "of a punishment",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a painful punishment",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "with a punishment",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَذِرُوا",
        "answer": "make excuse",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taʿtadhirū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْتَذِرُونَ",
        "answer": "They will make excuses",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿtadhirūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَذِرُوا",
        "answer": "make excuse",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taʿtadhirū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعَذِّرُونَ",
        "answer": "the ones who make excuses",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-muʿadhirūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the bedouins",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابُ",
        "answer": "The bedouins",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "al-aʿrābu",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the bedouins",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the bedouins",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the bedouins",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the bedouins",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Throne",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُعْرِضُوا",
        "answer": "that you may turn away",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "lituʿ'riḍū",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَعْرِضُوا",
        "answer": "So turn away",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fa-aʿriḍū",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَضًا",
        "answer": "a gain",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ʿaraḍan",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) averse",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَرَفُوا",
        "answer": "(who have) acknowledged",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tarafū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "(is) the right",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "Grievous",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُسْرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) difficulty",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-ʿus'rati",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "Then perhaps",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "faʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَى",
        "answer": "Perhaps",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشَرَ",
        "answer": "(is) twelve",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿashara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَشِيرَتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your relatives",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "waʿashīratukum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْطُوا",
        "answer": "they pay",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'ṭū",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُعْطُوا",
        "answer": "they are given",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "uʿ'ṭū",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْطَوْا",
        "answer": "they are given",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'ṭaw",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْظَمُ",
        "answer": "(are) greater",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aʿẓamu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Great",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَا",
        "answer": "(May) Allah forgive",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ʿafā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْفُ",
        "answer": "We pardon",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "naʿfu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَعْقَبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "So He penalized them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-aʿqabahum",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "but know",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "then know",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) do not know",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) know",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمِ",
        "answer": "Allah made evident",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "yaʿlami",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "And know",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "and you knew",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "wataʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُهُمْ",
        "answer": "you know them",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "taʿlamuhum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْلَمُهُمْ",
        "answer": "[We] know them",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "naʿlamuhum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "And know",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "wa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّامُ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "551",
        "tlit": "ʿallāmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "692",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "693",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "694",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "695",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "696",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "697",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "698",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "699",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "700",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "701",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "702",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Knower",
        "pcklId": "825",
        "tlit": "ʿālimi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Knower",
        "pcklId": "826",
        "tlit": "ʿālimi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُلْيَا",
        "answer": "the highest",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-ʿul'yā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمُرُوا",
        "answer": "they maintain",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿmurū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمُرُ",
        "answer": "will maintain",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿmuru",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِمَارَةَ",
        "answer": "and (the) maintenance",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waʿimārata",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْمَلُوا",
        "answer": "Do",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "iʿ'malū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) their deeds",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "aʿmāluhum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their deeds",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "aʿmālihim",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) their deeds",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "aʿmāluhum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your deeds",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "ʿamalakum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلًا",
        "answer": "a deed",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "ʿamalan",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your deed",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "ʿamalakum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلٌ",
        "answer": "(as) a deed",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "ʿamalun",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَامِلِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who collect",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿāmilīna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَنِتُّمْ",
        "answer": "you suffer",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿanittum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنْدَ",
        "answer": "and with",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "waʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "with Him",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِهِ",
        "answer": "[near] Him",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "ʿindihi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you made a covenant",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿāhadttum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have a covenant",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿāhadttum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you made a covenant",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿāhadttum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدَ",
        "answer": "made a covenant",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿāhada",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their treaty",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ʿahdahum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدٌ",
        "answer": "a covenant",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ʿahdun",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their treaty",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ʿahdihim",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَهْدِهِ",
        "answer": "to his promise",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "biʿahdihi",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَادٍ",
        "answer": "and Aad",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "waʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامِهِمْ",
        "answer": "this, their (final) year",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿāmihim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامًا",
        "answer": "one year",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿāman",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامًا",
        "answer": "(another) year",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿāman",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامٍ",
        "answer": "year",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿāmin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْلَةً",
        "answer": "poverty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿaylatan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْيُنُهُمْ",
        "answer": "with their eyes",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿyunuhum",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْرَمًا",
        "answer": "(as) a loss",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maghraman",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْغَارِمِينَ",
        "answer": "and for those in debt",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wal-ghārimīna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرَ",
        "answer": "will Allah forgive",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yaghfira",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "Ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "is'taghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "tastaghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "you ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "tastaghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَغْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "they ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yastaghfirū",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتِغْفَارُ",
        "answer": "(the) asking of forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "is'tigh'fāru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاغْلُظْ",
        "answer": "and be stern",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ugh'luẓ",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "غِلْظَةً",
        "answer": "harshness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghil'ẓatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah had enriched them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aghnāhumu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُغْنِ",
        "answer": "availed",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tugh'ni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُغْنِيكُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will enrich you",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yugh'nīkumu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنِيَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) rich",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "aghniyāu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَارِ",
        "answer": "the cave",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ghāri",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغَارَاتٍ",
        "answer": "caves",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "maghārātin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُيُوبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-ghuyūbi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(can) not",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(can) not",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "other than you",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ghayrakum",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغِيظُ",
        "answer": "that angers",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaghīẓu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْظَ",
        "answer": "(the) anger",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ghayẓa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْتِنِّي",
        "answer": "put me to trial",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taftinnī",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْتَنُونَ",
        "answer": "are tried",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yuf'tanūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفِتْنَةَ",
        "answer": "dissension",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-fit'nata",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفِتْنَةَ",
        "answer": "dissension",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-fit'nata",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفِتْنَةِ",
        "answer": "the trial",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-fit'nati",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِحَ",
        "answer": "Rejoice",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fariḥa",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) rejoicing",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fariḥūna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيضَةً",
        "answer": "an obligation",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "farīḍatan",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْرَقُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) are afraid",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yafraqūna",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِرْقَةٍ",
        "answer": "group",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fir'qatin",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a party",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "farīqin",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَفْرِيقًا",
        "answer": "and (for) division",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "watafrīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُفَصِّلُ",
        "answer": "And We explain in detail",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wanufaṣṣilu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفِضَّةَ",
        "answer": "and the silver",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wal-fiḍata",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His bounty",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْفُقَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "(are) for the poor",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "lil'fuqarāi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "they understand",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَتَفَقَّهُوا",
        "answer": "that they may obtain understanding",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "liyatafaqqahū",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَائِزُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the successful",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-fāizūna",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their mouths",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bi-afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their mouths",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bi-afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their mouths",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bi-afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفِيضُ",
        "answer": "flowing",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tafīḍu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْرِهِ",
        "answer": "his grave",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qabrihi",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْبِضُونَ",
        "answer": "and they close",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayaqbiḍūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقْبَلَ",
        "answer": "is accepted",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tuq'bala",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْبَلُ",
        "answer": "(Who) accepts",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaqbalu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتَقَبَّلَ",
        "answer": "will be accepted",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yutaqabbala",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(were) before them",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "then kill",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "fa-uq'tulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they slay",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "fayaqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُقْتَلُونَ",
        "answer": "and they are slain",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wayuq'talūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "then fight",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "faqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَاتِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you fight",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "tuqātilūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتِلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "Fight them ",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "qātilūhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "Fight",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "qātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتَلَهُمُ",
        "answer": "(May) Allah destroy them",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "qātalahumu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "And fight",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "waqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "they fight you",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūnakum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "will you fight",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "tuqātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَ",
        "answer": "They fight",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتِلُوا",
        "answer": "Fight",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "qātilū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "and the Quran",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wal-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "so let them not come near",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaqrabū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرُبَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(as) means of nearness",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "qurubātin",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "near of kin",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْبَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a means of nearness",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "qur'batun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبًا",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "qarīban",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَرَفْتُمُوهَا",
        "answer": "that you have acquired",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "iq'taraftumūhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاصِدًا",
        "answer": "easy",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qāṣidan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْطَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they cross",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaqṭaʿūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَطَّعَ",
        "answer": "(are) cut into pieces",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taqaṭṭaʿa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاقْعُدُوا",
        "answer": "and sit (in wait)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-uq'ʿudū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْعُدُوا",
        "answer": "Sit",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "uq'ʿudū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْعُدُوا",
        "answer": "so sit",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-uq'ʿudū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَدَ",
        "answer": "and sat",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waqaʿada",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَقْعَدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "in their staying",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "bimaqʿadihim",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقُعُودِ",
        "answer": "with sitting",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "bil-quʿūdi",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاعِدِينَ",
        "answer": "those who sit",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-qāʿidīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاعِدِينَ",
        "answer": "those who sit",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-qāʿidīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَلَّبُوا",
        "answer": "and had upset",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waqallabū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْقَلَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you returned",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "inqalabtum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their hearts",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُ",
        "answer": "(the) hearts",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "qulūbu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "qulūbahum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلٌ",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "qalīlun",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "(for) a little price",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "and it was said",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "yaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "and they say",
        "pcklId": "513",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "514",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "surely they will say",
        "pcklId": "516",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "517",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "(that) they said nothing",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "522",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتَ",
        "answer": "you said",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "qul'ta",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلِ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "526",
        "tlit": "waquli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "527",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "528",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their saying",
        "pcklId": "1647",
        "tlit": "qawluhum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلَ",
        "answer": "the saying",
        "pcklId": "1648",
        "tlit": "qawla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُمْ",
        "answer": "you stand",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taqum",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُمْ",
        "answer": "stand",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "taqum",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُومَ",
        "answer": "you stand",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "taqūma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامَ",
        "answer": "and establishes",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُقِيمُونَ",
        "answer": "and they establish",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wayuqīmūna",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "they are upright",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "is'taqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "then you be upright",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a people",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "(with) a people",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and (the) people",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "waqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoing people",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their people",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "qawmahum",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَيِّمُ",
        "answer": "the upright",
        "pcklId": "558",
        "tlit": "l-qayimu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "enduring",
        "pcklId": "610",
        "tlit": "muqīmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "enduring",
        "pcklId": "611",
        "tlit": "muqīmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةً",
        "answer": "(in) strength",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "quwwatan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَكْبَرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the greater Pilgrimage",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-akbari",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرَةً",
        "answer": "big",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "kabīratan",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "Allah has decreed",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "is recorded",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُتِبَ",
        "answer": "is recorded",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "kutiba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) ordinance",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and most of them",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْثَرَ",
        "answer": "and more abundant",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wa-akthara",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثْرَتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your multitude",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "kathratukum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةٍ",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "kathīratin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "lie",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yakdhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَبُوا",
        "answer": "lied",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely liars",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَاذِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the liars",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "l-kādhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely liars",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِهَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers dislike (it)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kariha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِهَ",
        "answer": "dislike (it)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "kariha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِهَ",
        "answer": "Allah disliked",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kariha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَرِهُوا",
        "answer": "and they disliked",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wakarihū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرْهًا",
        "answer": "unwillingly",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "karhan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَارِهُونَ",
        "answer": "disliked (it)",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "kārihūna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَارِهُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) unwilling",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "kārihūna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَادَهَا",
        "answer": "a decline (in) it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kasādahā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُسَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) lazy",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kusālā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "kafartum",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "and disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "wakafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "and the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "wal-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "l-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "l-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارِ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "l-kufāri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] disbelief",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "[with] disbelief",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "bil-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] disbelief",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "the disbelief",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the disbelief",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفْرًا",
        "answer": "(in) disbelief",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "kuf'ran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُفْرًا",
        "answer": "and (for) disbelief",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "wakuf'ran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers dislike (it)",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "bil-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "440",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافَّةً",
        "answer": "all together",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kāffatan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافَّةً",
        "answer": "all together",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "kāffatan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافَّةً",
        "answer": "all together",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "kāffatan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "(at) every",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّهِ",
        "answer": "all religions",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "kullihi",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) every",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلَامَ",
        "answer": "(the) Words of Allah",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "kalāma",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "kalimata",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَلِمَةُ",
        "answer": "while (the) Word",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wakalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "kalimata",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْنِزُونَ",
        "answer": "hoard",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaknizūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَنَزْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you hoarded",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kanaztum",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْنِزُونَ",
        "answer": "hoard",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taknizūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادَ",
        "answer": "had nearly",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kāda",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "can (there) be",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(It) is not",
        "pcklId": "440",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "they are",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "are",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "it had been",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "[you] are",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they are",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "(that) you were",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were (to)",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُ",
        "answer": "it is",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "yaku",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely we will be",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "tlit": "walanakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they could",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "458",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكُنْ",
        "answer": "(to) be",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "nakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used (to)",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used (to)",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(it) is",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they be",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "468",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "and be",
        "pcklId": "469",
        "tlit": "wakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "it was",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "471",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "472",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُكْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and will be branded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fatuk'wā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلْجَأً",
        "answer": "a refuge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "malja-an",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلْجَأَ",
        "answer": "refuge",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "malja-a",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَلْعَبُ",
        "answer": "and playing",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wanalʿabu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَنَهُمُ",
        "answer": "And Allah has cursed them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "walaʿanahumu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْقَوْنَهُ",
        "answer": "when they will meet Him",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yalqawnahu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْمِزُكَ",
        "answer": "criticizes you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yalmizuka",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْمِزُونَ",
        "answer": "criticize",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yalmizūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَمْتَعُوا",
        "answer": "So they enjoyed",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tamtaʿū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَمْتَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you have enjoyed",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tamtaʿtum",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَمْتَعَ",
        "answer": "enjoyed",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "is'tamtaʿa",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعُ",
        "answer": "(is the) enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "matāʿu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدَّتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their term",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "muddatihim",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Madinah",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "of the Madinah",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَدُوا",
        "answer": "They persist",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "maradū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةً",
        "answer": "times",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "marratan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "twice",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "marratayni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةً",
        "answer": "once",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "marratan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "twice",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "marratayni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَضٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a disease",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "maraḍun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "the sick",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-marḍā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "the dominion",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَهُمْ",
        "answer": "prevents them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "manaʿahum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاتَ",
        "answer": "who dies",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "māta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَاتُوا",
        "answer": "and died",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wamātū",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَاتُوا",
        "answer": "And they die",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wamātū",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُمِيتُ",
        "answer": "and He causes death",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wayumītu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their wealth",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْوَالٌ",
        "answer": "and wealth",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wa-amwālun",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالَ",
        "answer": "(the) wealth",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "amwāla",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِكُمْ",
        "answer": "with your wealth",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālikum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their wealth",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "amwāluhum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالًا",
        "answer": "(in) wealth",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "amwālan",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their wealth",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "amwāluhum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their wealth",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their wealth",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "amwālihim",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْوَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their wealth",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wa-amwālahum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنَبِّئُهُمْ",
        "answer": "informing them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tunabbi-uhum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَّأَنَا",
        "answer": "Allah (has) informed us",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "nabba-anā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَأُ",
        "answer": "(the) news",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "naba-u",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيَّ",
        "answer": "the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-nabiya",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيُّ",
        "answer": "O Prophet",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّبِيِّ",
        "answer": "for the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "lilnnabiyyi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيِّ",
        "answer": "the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَسٌ",
        "answer": "(are) unclean",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "najasun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their secret conversation",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wanajwāhum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُنْذِرُوا",
        "answer": "and that they may warn",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waliyundhirū",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "be revealed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "tunazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "and sent down",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "wa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "Then Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "fa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَتْ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "unzilat",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "Allah (has) revealed",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَتْ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "unzilat",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَتْ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "unzilat",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّسِيءُ",
        "answer": "the postponing",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-nasīu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "They forget",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَسِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "so He has forgotten them",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fanasiyahum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَبٌ",
        "answer": "fatigue",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "naṣabun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَحُوا",
        "answer": "they (are) sincere",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "naṣaḥū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْصُرْكُمْ",
        "answer": "and give you victory",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wayanṣur'kum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَرَكُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah helped you",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "naṣarakumu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْصُرُوهُ",
        "answer": "you help him",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tanṣurūhu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَرَهُ",
        "answer": "Allah helped him",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "naṣarahu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّصَارَى",
        "answer": "the Christians",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "a helper",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْصَارِ",
        "answer": "and the helpers",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "wal-anṣāri",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "naṣīrin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْصَارِ",
        "answer": "and the helpers",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "wal-anṣāri",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَظَرَ",
        "answer": "look",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "naẓara",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) bliss",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "naʿīmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "go forth",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "infirū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "you go forth",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tanfirū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "Go forth",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "infirū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "go forth",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tanfirū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَنْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "that they go forth",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "liyanfirū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَرَ",
        "answer": "go forth",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nafara",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their lives",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for yourselves",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "li-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your lives",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their own selves",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their lives",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their souls",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their lives",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their souls",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their lives",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their lives",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their own souls",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their lives",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "bi-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "his life",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَهَا",
        "answer": "spend it",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūnahā",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "Spend",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they (can) spend",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they (could) spend",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُ",
        "answer": "he spends",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yunfiqu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُ",
        "answer": "he spends",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yunfiqu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَقَاتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their contributions",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "nafaqātuhum",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَقَةً",
        "answer": "any spending",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "nafaqatan",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِفَاقًا",
        "answer": "(with) hypocrisy",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "nifāqan",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنِفَاقًا",
        "answer": "and hypocrisy",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "wanifāqan",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّفَاقِ",
        "answer": "the hypocrisy",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-nifāqi",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنَافِقَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the hypocrite women",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "wal-munāfiqātu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنَافِقَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the hypocrite women",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wal-munāfiqāti",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقُونَ",
        "answer": "The hypocrite men",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "al-munāfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqīna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrite men",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqīna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنَافِقِينَ",
        "answer": "and the hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wal-munāfiqīna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنَافِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) hypocrites",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "munāfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْقُصُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they have failed you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanquṣūkum",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقَمُوا",
        "answer": "they were resentful",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "naqamū",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَثُوا",
        "answer": "they break",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nakathū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَثُوا",
        "answer": "who broke",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nakathū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُنْكَرِ",
        "answer": "the wrong",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bil-munkari",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْكَرِ",
        "answer": "the wrong",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-munkari",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْكَرِ",
        "answer": "the wrong",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-munkari",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْهَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and forbid",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wayanhawna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْهَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and forbid",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wayanhawna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْتَهُونَ",
        "answer": "cease",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yantahūna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّاهُونَ",
        "answer": "and those who forbid",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wal-nāhūna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارَ",
        "answer": "(is the) Fire",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارَ",
        "answer": "Fire",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارُ",
        "answer": "(The) Fire",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارِ",
        "answer": "(the) Fire",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورَ",
        "answer": "Allah s light",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "nūra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورَهُ",
        "answer": "His Light",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "nūrahu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَالُوا",
        "answer": "they could attain",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yanālū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَالُونَ",
        "answer": "they inflict",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yanālūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَيْلًا",
        "answer": "an infliction",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "naylan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَاجَرُوا",
        "answer": "and emigrated",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wahājarū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهَاجِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the emigrants",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-muhājirīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُهَاجِرِينَ",
        "answer": "and the emigrants",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wal-muhājirīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "He has guided them",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "hadāhum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "with the guidance",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "the guided ones",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "l-muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَهْزِئُوا",
        "answer": "Mock",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "is'tahziū",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "mocking",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "They destroy",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yuh'likūna",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَمُّوا",
        "answer": "and determined",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wahammū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَمُّوا",
        "answer": "and planned",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wahammū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْهَارَ",
        "answer": "so it collapsed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-in'hāra",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَارٍ",
        "answer": "(about to) collapse",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "hārin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْتُمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you find them",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wajadttumūhum",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "they could find",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yajidūna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "find",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yajidūna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "they find",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yajidūna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِدُ",
        "answer": "I find",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "they find",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "and let them find",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "walyajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدًا",
        "answer": "One God",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wāḥidan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادِيًا",
        "answer": "a valley",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wādiyan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرْنَا",
        "answer": "Leave us",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "dharnā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَأَوْضَعُوا",
        "answer": "and would have been active",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wala-awḍaʿū",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطَئُونَ",
        "answer": "they step",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṭaūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُوَاطِئُوا",
        "answer": "to adjust",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "liyuwāṭiū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْطِئًا",
        "answer": "any step",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mawṭi-an",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَاطِنَ",
        "answer": "regions",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mawāṭina",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "(Has been) promised",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدُوهُ",
        "answer": "they had promised Him",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "waʿadūhu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَهَا",
        "answer": "he had promised it",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "waʿadahā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِدَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a promise",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "mawʿidatin",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "A promise",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْفَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) more faithful",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "awfā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "they should fear",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "the righteousness",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "righteousness",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "of the righteous",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "bil-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "those who fear (Him)",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَتَوَكَّلِ",
        "answer": "[so] let the believers put (their) trust",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "falyatawakkali",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَكَّلْتُ",
        "answer": "I put my trust",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tawakkaltu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيجَةً",
        "answer": "(as) intimates",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "walījatan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their children",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "awlāduhum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْلَادًا",
        "answer": "and children",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wa-awlādan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْلَادُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their children",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-awlāduhum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) close to you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yalūnakum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turned back",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "surely, they would turn",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "lawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "tawallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "takes them as allies",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yatawallahum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَتَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "And they turn away",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wayatawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yatawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "and turned away",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "watawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "They turned back",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْلَانَا",
        "answer": "(is) our Protector",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "mawlānā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) allies",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) allies",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "awliyāu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٍّ",
        "answer": "protector",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "waliyyin",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "by your hands",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدٍ",
        "answer": "willingly",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yadin",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِينَا",
        "answer": "by our hands",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīnā",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "aydiyahum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their oaths",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "aymānahum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانَ",
        "answer": "oaths",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aymāna",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their oaths",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "aymānahum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) day",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "and (on the) day",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "in the Day",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bil-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(from the) Day",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "day",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "9",
        "ayah": "108"
    }
]; 
export default words;